const questionsMiddle = [
    {
        category: "Web Development",
        type: "multiple",
        difficulty: "middle",
        question: "What is the purpose of HTML in web development?",
        correct_answer: "Structure the content of a website",
        incorrect_answers: [
          "Add interactivity and dynamic elements to a website",
          "Define the style and layout of a website",
          "Make a website interactive",
        ],
      },
      {
        category: "Science: Computers",
        type: "multiple",
        difficulty: "middle",
        question: "Which of the following is NOT a valid data type in JavaScript?",
        correct_answer: "Array",
        incorrect_answers: [
          "Boolean",
          "Number",
          "String",
        ],
      },
      {
        category: "Web Development",
        type: "multiple",
        difficulty: "middle",
        question: "What does the 'function' keyword signify in JavaScript?",
        correct_answer: "Declaring a reusable block of code",
        incorrect_answers: [
          "A built-in method",
          "A loop statement",
          "A data type",
        ],
      },
      {
        category: "Web Development",
        type: "multiple",
        difficulty: "middle",
        question: "In HTML, what tag is used to create a hyperlink?",
        correct_answer: "<a> ",
        incorrect_answers: [
          "<src>",
          "<link>",
          "<href>",
        ],
      },
      {
        category: "Web Development",
        type: "multiple",
        difficulty: "middle",
        question: "Which CSS property is used to create space between an element's border and its content?",
        correct_answer: "Padding",
        incorrect_answers: [
          "Margin",
          "Border-spacing",
          "Space"
        ],
      },
      {
        category: "Web Development",
        type: "multiple",
        difficulty: "middle",
        question: "What symbol is used for single-line comments in JavaScript?",
        correct_answer: "// ",
        incorrect_answers: [
          "--!>",
          "/*",
          "<!--",
        ],
      },
      {
        category: "Web Development",
        type: "multiple",
        difficulty: "middle",
        question: "What is the purpose of the <script> tag in HTML?",
        correct_answer: "Write JavaScript code within an HTML document",
        incorrect_answers: [
          "Load external images",
          "Style the content of a webpage",
          "Link to an external CSS file",
        ],
      },
      {
        category: "Web Development",
        type: "multiple",
        difficulty: "middle",
        question: "What JavaScript function is used to print content to the console for debugging?",
        correct_answer: "A) console.log() ",
        incorrect_answers: [
          "print()",
          "log()",
          "write()",
        ],
      },
      {
        category: "Web Development",
        type: "multiple",
        difficulty: "middle",
        question: "Which HTML tag is used to define the structure of a table?",
        correct_answer: "<table>",
        incorrect_answers: [
          "<tr>",
          "<row>",
          "<tab>",
        ],
      },
      {
        category: "Web Development",
        type: "boolean",
        difficulty: "middle",
        question: "HTML is responsible for the structure of a webpage, while CSS is responsible for the presentation of the content on the webpage.",
        correct_answer: "True ",
        incorrect_answers: ["False"]
      },
      {
        category: "Web Development",
        type: "boolean",
        difficulty: "middle",
        question: "JavaScript is a server-side scripting language that helps with the functionality of a website.",
        correct_answer: "False",
        incorrect_answers: ["True "]
      },
      {
        category: "Web Development",
        type: "boolean",
        difficulty: "middle",
        question: "In HTML, the '<head>' tag is where you would typically find the content that is directly displayed on the webpage.",
        correct_answer: "False",
        incorrect_answers: ["True "]
      },
      {
        category: "Web Development",
        type: "boolean",
        difficulty: "middle",
        question: "CSS can be directly embedded within an HTML file using the '<css>' tag.",
        correct_answer: "False",
        incorrect_answers: ["True "]
      },
      {
        category: "Web Development",
        type: "boolean",
        difficulty: "middle",
        question: "Inline CSS is when you apply CSS styling directly within the HTML element using the 'style' attribute.",
        correct_answer: "True ",
        incorrect_answers: ["False"]
      },
      {
        category: "Web Development",
        type: "boolean",
        difficulty: "middle",
        question: "HTML is not a programming language but a markup language used to structure content on the web.",
        correct_answer: "True ",
        incorrect_answers: ["False"]
      },
      {
        category: "Web Development",
        type: "boolean",
        difficulty: "middle",
        question: "JavaScript is mainly used for client-side scripting to make web pages interactive.",
        correct_answer: "True",
        incorrect_answers: ["False"]
      },
      {
        category: "Web Development",
        type: "boolean",
        difficulty: "middle",
        question: "CSS stands for Central Style Sheets, which is a way to globally style web pages across different websites.",
        correct_answer: "False",
        incorrect_answers: ["True "]
      },
      {
        category: "Web Development",
        type: "boolean",
        difficulty: "middle",
        question: "JavaScript is mandatory for creating interactive elements on a webpage, such as buttons that trigger specific actions.",
        correct_answer: "True ",
        incorrect_answers: ["False"]
      },
      {
        category: "Web Development",
        type: "boolean",
        difficulty: "middle",
        question: "The use of external CSS files allows for consistent styling across multiple HTML pages.",
        correct_answer: "True ",
        incorrect_answers: ["False"]
      }
    ];